Fox Theater Memories Project Records, 1883-2011 (bulk 1925-2008)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Oral History media, 2001-2008
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 2, Chandelier and metal detection, Erma Duran, Workday, 2001, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 3, Lighting, Floresco, J.B. Steel, Stars, 2001, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 4, 2nd Annual 'Light up the Fox' Gala, Mother's Day Open House, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 5, Board of Directors meeting, H. Oyama, Bob Morrison, Roy Noggle, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 6, Board of Directors meeting, Tim Young, Keith Walker, Glen McCrealey, Chris Larsen, 2001, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 7, Andy McWhirlton, Herb/Stratford, Jennifer Mix, Peggy Johnson, Work Day, 2001, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 8, Gala, Stars, interior renovation, Mike Carpenter, Evergreen, 2002, 2003, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 9, Marquee installation, Flag installation, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 10, Curtis/Wixen wedding, Graham Davis, Old Star building, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 11, Marquee relighting, Graham Davis, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 12, Gala, E. Bellamy, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 13, Fox construction, Ribbon Cutting, Mechanical Room demolition, VIP Tour by Ben Buehler, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 14, Lobby ceiling, Open House, clean-up, 2003, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 15, Last Work Day, 5th Annual 'Light up the Fox' Gala, Work Day, chandeliers, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 16A, Pima College Forum, part 1, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 16B, Pima College Forum, part 2, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 16C, City High School partnership, Introduction to Theatre and to Memories Project, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 17, Fox volunteer luncheon, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 18B, Lobby/ceiling restoration tour with B.C. McKinney, renovation to date, City High interviews, 2004, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 19, 75th Annual Street Fair, Nickolay Serafimov, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 20, Unveiling front lobby, interior progress, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 21, Grand Opening New Year's Eve, Camera: Rudy Reuser, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Fox Restoration Tape No. 22, Open House, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Fox Video 1 - Background, clouds, demo, snow/Catalinas, 2001, 2002, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 25)